delicious?
美味しい?
Yeah, it's really delicious.
うん、めちゃめちゃ美味しい
Do you know how much it costs?
それいくらするか知ってる?
picture?
え?
i don't know.
知らない
Because they say it's okay to drink.
だって飲んでいいよって言うから
I drank it.
飲んじゃった
That's 3000 yen right away.
それ3000円すぐに
Isn't that a lie?
嘘でしょ?
picture?
え?
Is it okay?
いいの?
I did drink it though.
飲んじゃったけど
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Please taste and drink.
味わって飲んでください
It's insanely delicious.
めちゃめちゃ美味しい
delicious?
美味しい?
a little bit...
ちょっと...
Yeah.
うん
How many months has it been?
何ヶ月ぶりだ?
It's probably been 2 or 3 months.
2、3ヶ月ぶりかな
Hey?
ねえ?
I was busy.
バタバタしてた
Pretty much me.
結構私が
Has it been a long time since then?
結構あれから?
I was busy.
バタバタしてた
Yeah, yeah.
そうそう そう
I said that I had quit being a caster, and...
キャスターはやめたって言って、 で、
I was looking for a job, and then I happened to meet someone I knew.
就活とかもしてて、 したら、たまたま知り合いの人に ちょっと
Would you like to try modeling?
モ デルやってみない?
Like.
みたいな
picture?
え?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
She's really amazing, but she's not the kind of model you'd see in a magazine.
めっちゃすごい、雑誌とかに載るようなモデルじゃないんだけど
Isn't that something naughty?
なんかそれ、やらしいやつじゃないの?
No!
違うよ!
different.
違う
I wonder what's going on during this time.
この間も、何だっけな
It's kind of like an advertisement.
なんかのね、広告みたいに出してもらって
Is it cosmetics?
化粧品かな?
I might ask them to give me a little bit.
ちょっとだけ出してもらったりとか
That's amazing.
すごいじゃん
It's crazy, yeah, I'm not that famous, but...
め ちゃめちゃ、そう、有名ってほどじゃないんだけどね、
still.
まだ
I haven't done such a big job yet,
そんな大きい仕事とかはまだだけど、
I want to do my best from now on.
これから頑張っていきたいな、とは
Are you already active in Tokyo?
もう東京で活躍してんの?
Yes, that's right.
うん、そうだね
I guess it's almost like that.
ほとんどそうかな
And then there's the model, etc.
あとはなんかその、モデルとか、あとは、
Like an assistant.
アシスタントみたいな
I was given a little help or something.
ちょっとした手伝いとかさせてもらったりとか
It's quite fun.
結構楽しいよ
Oh, that office?
あ、その事務所?
That's right.
そうなんだ
That's why I was so busy that I didn't get to see you at all.
そうだから、忙しくて全然会えなかったからさ、
I was so happy to meet you on my day off.
休みに会ってすごい嬉しいなって思って
Really?
ほんとに?
Yeah.
うん
The atmosphere has changed somehow.
なんか雰囲気変わったよね
I guess so.
そうかな
Take care of your muscles, etc.
筋ケアとかは、気をつけたりとか、
Well, when it comes to makeup, I change things up or change my mood.
メイクはまあ、変えたりとか、 気分変わったりとか
What did it look like?
どんなっぽくなった?
That's what a classmate told me.
なんかね、同級生に言われた
I was told the same thing.
同じこと言われた
Were you told?
言われた?
Yeah.
うん
I happened to hear the sound of a classmate.
たまたま同級生の音あって
Hmm.
う ーん
It's amazing, it's changed.
なんか すごい、変わったよ
Okay, in a good way.
いいよ、いい意味で
In a good way?
いい意味で?
good.
よかった
There's also the fact that I'm doing that job,
その仕事とかしてるっていうのもあるし、
I'm surrounded by beautiful people, so I feel like I need to be beautiful too.
周りが綺麗な人ばっかだから、 自分も綺麗にならなきゃとは思う
hey.
ね
I tried to be careful, really.
気 をつけるようにやった、めっちゃ
I think so, certainly.
それは思うね、確かに
Because there's a really beautiful person next to me,
だってすごい綺麗な人が横にいてさ、
But my skin feels a little dull,
でも自分ちょっと肌が歩いてるとか、
I can't help but feel embarrassed.
もう恥ずかしくてしょうがないからね
I see.
そっか
I will continue to do my best.
これからもちょっと頑張っていく
It's toned, isn't it?
引き締まるよね
Are you already dyed in the colors of the city?
もうじゃあ、都会の色に染まってきちゃった?
Eh, that much!?
えっ、そこまで!?
I still think it's just my stomach.
まだなんか、お腹でやがるとか思うけど
Isn't he doing something like papacas?
なんかパパカスとかしてんじゃないの?
I haven't done it, stop it.
してない、やめて
Well, my friend also told me,
なんか さ、友達にも言われたの、
I think that's probably the thing about clothes, too.
服装とかも多分あれなんだと思うんだけど、
I haven't done it, and I don't want to, so I really need to stop doing it.
してないし、したくないから、本当にやめて
He said he was invited by a great person when he was a newscaster.
なんか偉い人、 キャスターの時に偉い人に誘われたとか言ってた
From.
から さ
I stopped doing it because I didn't like it.
それが嫌でやめてやめちゃったからさ
That's right.
そっかそっか
I would hate it if that happened to me too.
こっちらもそれあったら嫌だよ
Give me a break.
勘弁して
Isn't there one at the moment?
今のところないの?
No, no.
ないない
I'm worried.
心配だよ
There isn't.
ないよ
After all, various companies are changing when it comes to shooting advertisements.
やっぱさ、広告とか撮るのにいろんな企業が変わってるから、
I was invited to a party at the company,
その企業のパーティーにちょっと呼ばれたりは、
Lately, that's what I've been buzzing about the most,
最近それが一番あれでバタバタバタバタしてたんだけど、
Partly because I was originally a caster.
もともとキャスターやってたっていうのもあって
I see.
そ っか
So I guess so.
だからそうかな
As for manners, I remember everything,
マナーとかはね、さすがに一通り全部覚えてたから、
I don't know if I'm anticipating that, but
それを見越してか分かんないけど、
I think there were quite a few people I wanted to follow along with.
ちょっとついてきてみたいなのは割とあったかな
That's right.
そうなんだ
Yes, I was flopping around, but I couldn't wear high heels.
うん、バタバタして、でもさ、ハイヒールとかなれなくてさ、
It's really tiring.
めちゃめちゃ疲れるんだよね
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Yeah, I'm used to crying, but I'm not used to crying at first.
うん、泣き慣れて、最初なんて泣き慣れてないから、
If I don't have an escort, if I'm not involved in something,
エスコートの人いないと、何かにつかわってないと、
Oops!
おっと!
Like.
みたいな
It's so cute, it's just for an invitation.
せっかく可愛いさ、ちょっとお呼ばれ用のさ、
I was wearing something like a dress.
ワンピースみたいなの着たりしてさ、
Even though she's wearing cute high heel shoes,
可愛らしいハイヒールの靴貼ってるのに、
Oops!
おっと!
That's a bit lame, isn't it?
ってなるのはちょっとダサいでしょ
Well, well, that's right.
まあまあまあ、そっかそっか
yes.
そう
You're making an effort.
努力してんだね
It was amazing, really.
すごしかったね、ほんとに
But it was nice to meet you.
でも会えてよかったわ
Really, I feel like I finally met someone.
ね、ほんと、やっとなんか会えたって感じ
I'm glad you say that.
嬉しい、そんな言ってくれるの
Hey, wow, this room is amazing.
ちょっとさ、すごいさ、この部屋すごいんだよ
what?
何?
Oh, yeah, I was curious because the curtains were closed.
え、そう、カーテン閉まってるから気になってたの
Yes, that's right, stand up for a moment.
そうそうそう、ちょっとじゃあ立ってさ、
Would you please open this?
ちょっとこれ、開けてごらん?
this?
これ?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Wow, that’s amazing!
え、すごい!
Wait a minute, it won't open.
ちょっと待って、開かない
Can this be opened in the main hall?
これ、主堂で開けるやつ?
Oh, open it.
あ、開くんだ
Hey there.
ほ らほら
Wow, that’s amazing!
え、すごい!
Wait a minute, isn't that a score tree?
ちょっと待って、あれスコアツリーでしょ?
be?
ある?
Look, the score tree is right in front of you.
え、目の前スコアツリーだよ、ほら
picture?
え?
Wow, that's amazing.
え、すごーい
copper?
どう?
No, this is already a surprise.
いや、これはもう、え、びっくり
Surprised?
びっくり?
Surprised.
びっくり
I don't usually see things like this.
普段こんなの見ないもんだって
Well, I guess I've gotten used to this kind of scenery.
いや、 もうこういう景色に慣れちゃったのかなって
I'm not used to it. I'm not used to it.
慣れてない慣れてない
Listen to me.
話聞いてて
I'm not used to it. I'm not used to it.
慣れてない慣れてない
I was worried.
心配だったんだけど
It's true that people will find out about the party, but
確かにその、パーティーとかバレたりするけど、
Even if I was called, I ended up talking to everyone,
呼ばれたとしても結局みんなと話したりとか、
Yes, I have to talk to you,
そう、お話しなきゃいけないから、
I don't have a chance to see outside.
外なんて見る機会ないの
Ah, I see.
あ、そっか
I'd like to see it.
見たいんだけどね
There were some absolutely beautiful places.
絶対綺麗なところとか何か所かあったから
Okay, okay, just a second.
いいでしょ、いいでしょ、ちょっと
So beautiful.
すっごい綺麗
That's amazing.
すごいね
Well, I'd say it's turning nice and pink.
え、いい感じにピンクになってるって言うな
The sunset is beautiful, isn't it?
夕日がさ、綺麗でしょ
Look over there, because it's already glowing with the reflection of the setting sun.
あそこ見て、だってもう夕日反射して光ってるからね
Wow, that's amazing.
え、すごいな
This must be really beautiful at night.
これ夜になったらめちゃめちゃ綺麗なんだろうな
It's still beautiful though.
今も綺麗だけど
I agree.
そうだね
I'm looking forward to it, huh?
楽しみだな、ちょっと
Today, here, what?
今日はさ、ここでさ、 何?
Stay overnight.
お泊りしてさ
Are you staying the night?
お泊りして?
I thought we should play together.
一緒に遊ぼうかなって
I thought I might enjoy it.
楽しもうかなって
Your hands are cold.
手冷たいね
Because it's cold, cold clothing.
冷たい、冷衣装だから
Cold clothes?
冷衣装?
Cold clothes.
冷衣装
It might have been a little thin.
ちょっと薄かったかもしれない
what?
何?
Fukuga.
ふくが
Fukuga?
ふくが?
This looks great on you.
すごい似合ってるよ、これ
TRUE?
本当?
thank you.
ありがとう
It's amazing, you look like an adult in your clothes.
なんかすごい、服装も大人っぽいね
I'm already worried about it.
もうね、気にしまくりだよ
Are you worried?
気にしまくり?
I'm worried about it.
気にしまくりだよ
That never happened when I was a caster.
キャスターやってる時とか全然そんなことなかったのに
They're all beautiful kids.
綺麗な子たちばっかりだからさ
It's beautiful.
綺麗だよ
TRUE?
本当?
thank you.
ありがとう
happy.
嬉しい
There is a group that is working hard.
頑張ってる会がある
Is that so?
そうなの?
Yeah.
うん
tickles.
くすぐったい
tickles?
くすぐったい?
It's ticklish, amazing.
くすぐったい、すごい
what?
何?
It tickles so well.
あんまくすぐったい
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
My neck was ticklish though.
首くすぐったいなったけど
Neck tickling.
首くすぐったがり
What about your ears?
お耳は?
The ears...
耳は...
I've been feeling okay lately.
最近ちょっと大丈夫
I don't know.
分 かんないけど
I've never been touched like that.
そんな触られることないじゃん
Isn't it?
ないでしょ?
What are you doing?
何してんの?
Hey, wait a minute?
ねぇ、ちょっと?
what?
何?
What are you doing?
何をしてるんだって
no.
いや
Just a little.
ちょっとさ
what?
何?
Hey, it's the back window, but it's solid.
ねぇ、後ろ窓なんだけど、がっつり
Aren't you scared?
怖くない?
If you look down.
下見たら
It's not scary.
怖くはない
Aren't you scared?
怖くない?
It's okay though.
大丈夫だけど
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
There might be someone watching, I guess.
見てる人いるかもね、なんか
No way.
やだ
Hey, sit down.
ちょっとさ、腰かけて
Sit down.
腰かけて
It's so naughty.
いやらしいっすね
There are various accidents.
いろいろとアクシデントがある
accident?
アクシデント?
It was an accident.
アクシデントだった
Before you come, just a moment.
来る前にね、ちょっと
Broken down?
やぶけた?
Yes, I got caught on the train.
電車でそう、引っ掛けられちゃった
a little bit,
ちょっと、
It smells good.
いい 匂いする
picture?
え?
lie?
嘘?
I won't do anything.
なんもしないよ
Hey.
ねぇ
amazing.
すごい
what?
何?
You're a little sweaty.
ちょっと汗ばんでるね
lie?
嘘?
Yeah.
うん
picture?
え?
Isn't that a lie?
嘘でしょ?
picture?
え?
Tell me it's not like that.
そんなことないって言って
a little bit.
ちょっと
How sexy.
なんてセクシーな
Amazing, kind of.
すごい、なんか
Looks like it's going to fall.
落ちそう
Is it about to fall?
落ちそう?
Yeah.
うん
It's a little unbalanced.
ちょっとバランスが悪い
what?
何?
Will it go up?
上がる?
It's going up though.
上がるけど
picture?
え?
a little bit.
ちょっと
It's going up though.
上がるけどね
fault.
あら
Why this...
なんでこの...
Ta
タ
It's going to blow up.
イ ツやぶけちゃう
Will it fail?
やぶけちゃう?
I'm going to ruin it.
やぶけちゃう
It's already broken, isn't it?
やぶけてるでしょ、もう
I was disappointed though.
やぶけちゃったけど
what?
何?
amazing.
すごい
Really.
めっちゃ
I'm so embarrassed, but now.
すっごい恥ずかしいんだけど、今
Touch me where.
どこ触って
warm.
温かい
It's not warm.
温かくない
There's also body temperature.
体温もあるけど
already.
もう
It's warm here.
温かいじゃん、ここ
What do you mean by warm?
何温かいって、どういうこと?
My hands were cold though.
手は冷たかったけど
What are you doing?
何してんの?
Will this blow up?
これやぶける?
Ah, amazing.
あ、すごい
It doesn't break at all.
全然やぶけない
Will it not break?
やぶけない?
It was a shame.
残念でした
picture?
え?
Huh?
あれ?
amazing.
すごい
It's sturdy.
頑丈だ
what are you doing?
何をしているの?
what the hell.
いったい
Hey, hey, hey, wait, wait,
ねえ、ねえ、ねえ、待って、待って、
hang on.
待って
I'm torn, I'm torn.
ビリビリってる、ビリビリってる
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
ちょ、 ちょ、ちょ、ちょ
what?
何?
I was a little confused.
ちょっとやぶけた
It's not broken.
やぶけたじゃないし
Hey, what?
ねえ、何?
Why are you in trouble?
何でやぶいてんの?
Hey hey, I'm going home, I'm wearing my highs.
ねえねえ、帰りさ、履くさ、ハイツがさ、
There isn't.
ないじゃん
Are you going to wear them on your way home?
帰り、履くの?
Isn't that obvious?
当たり前でしょ?
This came in, me.
これ入ってきたんだよ、私
hey
ね
picture.
え
Oh, no, no, no.
あ、 やばいやばいやばい
Wait, wait, wait.
ちょっと待って、待って、待って
Wait, wait.
待って、待って
What are you doing?
何してんの?
what the hell.
いったい
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, biri biri biri.
ねえ、ねえ、ねえ、ねえ、ねえ、ビリビリビリビリ
what?
何?
That's crazy.
やぶじゃん
It's not crazy.
や ぶじゃんじゃないし
Hey, what are you doing?
ねえ、何をしているの?
what the hell.
いったい
It's tough, but this is it.
硬いね、でもこれね
After all, I bought one that wouldn't tear.
だって、破れないやつを買ったんだもん
Isn't that obvious?
当たり前でしょ?
It's not cheap.
安物じゃないね
安物じゃないよ
As expected of a celebrity.
さすが、芸能人
No, that's not true.
いや、違うって
After all, wouldn't it be a problem if you went out for a while and it broke?
だって、ちょっと出かけて破れちゃったら困るでしょ?
It would be a problem if it broke right away, right?
さっきですぐ破れちゃったら困るでしょ?
Not at all, because it didn't break.
ちょっと全然さ、破けなかったからさ
I can't give up.
やぶけないんだもん
I was like, ``I bought the Yabukenai.''
やぶけないの買ったんだもん、みたいなのと
Ah, I like how you take your clothes off.
あ いつ、脱ぐ姿いいね
What is that?
何のあれなの?
Is it a sexual fetish or something?
性癖とかそういうあれなの?
I can't see it that way.
それじゃ見えないよ
I mean, it's embarrassing, isn't it?
だって、恥ずかしいでしょ?
It's embarrassing because no one is watching.
恥ずかしいって、だって誰も見てないよ
That's not the problem.
そういう問題じゃないの
Take a look.
ちょっと見てくれ
I'm embarrassed to have done it so quickly, but
早くして、恥ずかしいんですけど、
This type
このタ
IP.
イ プ
Well then, look behind you.
じゃあ、後ろも見てさ
Look at this too.
こっちも見て
This way.
こっちやねん
I'm in Kuhi.
くひにいる
I'm embarrassed to have done it so quickly, but
早くして、恥ずかしいんですけど、
This type.
このタイプ
Hurry up, shame on you
早 く して、恥
It's a bit embarrassing, but this type.
ず かしいんですけど、このタイプ
Well then, look behind you.
じゃあ、後ろも見てさ
The same goes for the back.
後 ろも、そのまんま
Like this?
このまんま?
Ass, oh yeah.
お尻、あ、そう
Does that mean you should wrap your butt more?
お尻もっと巻くってことなんですか?
Come on, just get your hands on it.
ちょっとさ、手ついてさ
Without a butt.
お尻つきなしで
Look at this too.
こっちも見て
You have a beautiful butt.
きれいなお尻やねん
Very quick.
すごくすぐい
Look at this too.
こ っちも見て
lie?
嘘?
Really soon.
本当にすぐさ
Have you ever had sex in a place with such a beautiful view?
こんな景色いいとこでエッチしたことある?
There isn't.
ないよ
do not have?
ない?
first time?
初 めて?
I don't think it's normal.
普通はないと思う
It's become cute.
可愛くなったね
It gets cuter every time.
あるたび可愛くなってくね
TRUE?
本当?
what?
なに?
It's been a while since I last played with you.
久々にチューしちゃったね
what?
なに?
What is this hand?
この手はなに?
What on earth is this hand?
この手は一体なに?
this is ...
これは ...
Are you wearing underwear too?
下も着てる?
Because it's cold.
だって寒いもん
I have to wear it.
着ないと
It's see-through.
透けちゃうし
Huh?
あれ?
Hide it.
隠して
They'll find out you have it.
持ってるのバレちゃう
It's very thick.
すごく厚い
It's not thick.
厚くないです
This too?
これも?
Yeah.
うん
What kind of...
これどんな...
thank you.
ありがとう
Are you going to take off your bottom too?
下も脱ぐの?
cold.
寒い
So beautiful.
すごい綺麗
It's so cold.
めちゃめちゃ寒い
cold?
寒い?
It's cold.
冷たいとこ
It's true.
本当だ
warm.
温かい
warm?
温かい?
My hands were warm.
手が温かかった
But it's different.
違うんだけど
Are you excited?
興奮してるかな?
Yeah.
うん
Don't be so serious.
あんまマジマジと言わないで
It's been a while since I saw it.
久々に見た
I was fine.
元気だったよ
This isn't something you should do while doing this.
これしながらする話じゃないでしょ
absolute.
絶対
Hey, you took it off.
ねえ、外したでしょ
picture?
え?
You took it off.
外したでしょ
Did you notice?
気づいた?
I noticed.
気づいた
Because on my back...
だって背中の...
The thing on my back is gone.
背中のものがなくなったもん
Are you still embarrassed?
まだ恥ずかしいの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's obvious.
当たり前じゃん
Hey, why?
ねえ、なんで?
It's really cold though.
めちゃめちゃ寒いんだけど
cold.
冷たい
It's cold.
寒いもんだって
Your hands are cold, right?
手冷たいでしょ?
It's cold.
寒 いもんだって
cold.
冷たい
After all, it's cold in this outfit.
だって寒いもん、この格好は
What are you planning to do with this outfit?
こんな格好をさして、どうするつもりですか?
It's warm here.
ここ温かいよ
Is it just my imagination?
気のせいじゃないかな?
It's completely different from your hands.
手と全然違う
I wonder why?
なんでだろうね?
I haven't written it.
書いてないよ
yes?
そう?
I don't think it's written.
書いてないと思う
Then I have to check.
じゃあ確認しなきゃ
picture?
え?
How do I check?
どうやって確認するの?
It's not sweat.
汗じゃないじゃん
That's it.
だ ってそれは
That's different.
違うじゃん
It's not sweat, right?
汗じゃないでしょ?
a little bit.
ちょっと
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
what?
何?
This is it.
これさ
what?
何ですか?
Did you shave your head?
おケケ剃っちゃったの?
Yeah.
うん
Because you'll get wet somehow.
だってなんか濡れるから
why?
なんで?
Should we have met?
会った方がよかったの?
different.
違う
Because it's been around for a long time.
今までずっと生えてたからさ
I was wondering what happened.
どうしたのかなと思って
picture?
え?
I usually get wet on girls' days.
普通に女の子の日に 濡れちゃうから
It's so beautiful.
すごい綺麗だよ
I don't think you should take it that seriously.
そんなにマジマジと 見るもんじゃないじゃん
It's nice and fresh again.
また新鮮でいいね
already.
もう
After all, I've become an adult.
やっぱなんか大人れたわ
yeah?
ん?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Where are you saying it's been a while?
どこに久々って 言ってんの?
amazing.
すごい
since
自
It's a minute.
分 でさ
I don't always do that.
いつもしてないよ
I always do it.
いつもしてるよ
Open it properly later.
後でちゃんと開いて
I don't think you should take it too seriously.
そんなにマジマジと 見るもんじゃないから
I've always wanted to see it.
ずっと見たかったんだもん
good?
いい?
Not yet?
まだ ダメ?
Why?
なんでよ
Because it's open.
開いてるから
no.
いや
Don't just look.
見るだけじゃないよ
Please take a moment.
ちょっと足掛かえてごらん
Close your legs.
足閉じて
It doesn't go in at all.
全然入っていかないね
It's outside.
外じゃん
Please step here.
ここに足のっけてごらん
feet?
足?
oh yeah.
そうそう
It's getting dark.
暗くなっちゃったね
Wander around?
ぐるぐるする?
It's really messy.
すごいぐしゃぐしゃだね
Pussy.
おまんこね
Soaked.
びっちょり
That's pretty cool.
び っ ちょ りだね
amazing.
すごい
fault.
あら
That's amazing.
すごいね
You got cold because you got wet.
濡れちゃったから寒くなったでしょ
cold.
寒い
Now let's go take a bath.
じゃあお風呂入りに行こう
warm?
暖かい?
warm.
暖かい
It's pretty cool though.
ビカビカだけどね
I love this shower so much.
このシャワー好きすぎるね
I love you too much.
好きすぎるな
That's fine, but it doesn't make any sense.
良くてだけど、 意味ないよね
There's no point in coming back.
帰ってきたら意味ないよね
Let's wash together.
一緒に洗おうよ
I took a bath.
お風呂入った
I've accumulated it.
溜めたよ
I took a bath.
お風呂入った
enter?
入る?
enter.
入る
Come in?
入って?
Come in.
入って
It's a little long though.
ちょっと長いんだけど
It's cold.
寒いって
cold.
寒い
I wonder if it's warm.
暖かいかな
A little cool.
若干涼い
It's warm, but I don't think it will overflow.
暖かいけど、溢れないかな
Is it okay if we go in together?
二人で入ったら大丈夫?
hot.
熱い
It's okay.
大丈夫だね
It's designed to prevent it from overflowing.
溢 れないようになってるんだね
what?
なに?
It's designed to prevent it from overflowing.
溢れないようになってるんだね
I agree.
そうだね
What?
なんだ?
You'll get a little wet.
ちょっと濡るね
Hot water?
お 湯?
It's not my hot water.
俺のお湯じゃないよ
deep?
深い?
It warmed up a bit.
ちょっと温まった
You'll get a little wet.
ちょっと濡るでしょ
When it gets to the bottom, it's pretty deep.
下までつくと、 下までつくと結構深い
Drowning?
溺れる?
I'll drown.
溺れちゃう
There's something.
何かある
What is that?
何それ?
Let's add some bath salts.
バスソルト入れようぜ
What about bath salts?
バスソルトってやると?
Who will take it?
誰が取るの?
Doesn't it look like bath salts?
入浴剤みたいじゃない?
kana?
かな?
Apply bath salts to your skin,
バスソルトは、 これを肌につけて、
You should take it.
取ってやるといい
I agree.
そうだね
Are there any capsules you can get?
カプセルとかが取れるやつもあるの?
If you put it on.
つければ
That's because of bubbles.
あれだって、 泡
This is something that bubbles.
これ泡が立つやつ
It doesn't have jam, so I don't think it will foam.
ジャムついてないから、 泡立たない気がする
It's not on.
ついてないよね
Probably not.
ついてないよね、多分
Would you like to try it?
入れてみる?
Let's put it in.
入れてみよう
It's made of paper.
紙でできてる
It's made of paper, so the remaining parts,
紙でできてるから、 残ってる部分、
I become lazy.
しなしなになっちゃう
Does it smell good?
いい匂いする?
It smells good.
いい匂いする
What can I see?
何が見えるんだろう?
It says "original bath salts".
オリジナルバスソルトって書いてある
Is this the original?
ここオリジナルなのかな?
Shall we go?
いくよ?
amazing.
すごい
It contains something like salt.
塩みたいなのが入ってる
amazing.
すごい
It's falling.
落ちてきた
oh yeah.
そうそう
It can remove dirt and pore dirt.
汚れとか、 毛穴汚れみたいなのが取れる
It's not Reuben, is it?
ルーベンじゃないですよね
It doesn't slip at all.
だいじょうぶ滑らないよね
Really.
本当に
It's true, my teeth don't slip.
本当だって、 歯が滑らない
Is that so?
そうかな?
I haven't run it though.
流してないけど
Doesn't it slip?
滑らない?
No slipping.
滑らない
dangerous.
危ない
what are you doing?
何してるの?
No slipping.
滑らない
What should I do about this?
これどうすればいいの?
My feet are difficult.
足難しい
Is it getting warmer?
温かくなってきたの?
It's getting warmer, isn't it?
温かくなってきたでしょ?
It's getting warmer though.
温かくなってきたけど
Did you have any hobbies like that?
そういう趣味ありましたっけ?
There isn't.
ないよね
I feel like I'm being very shy.
すごい遠慮してる感じが
I've never experienced that once.
だ って一回したことないじゃん
I don't know.
わかんないもん
You'll refrain, right?
遠慮するでしょ、そりゃ
feet?
足?
picture?
え?
what?
何?
feet?
足?
What should I do?
どうすればいいの?
what?
何?
What are you doing?
何するの?
big.
大きい
They said it was big.
大きいって言われたって
It's big enough.
だ って十分大きい
Isn't that enough?
十分じゃないの?
what?
何?
Not big enough.
十分大きくない
It's embarrassing though.
恥ずかしいんだけど
warm.
温かい
It's a little bubbling.
ちょっと泡立ってる
It's going to be amazing when it gets cold.
寒くなったらすごいことになりそう
Please put it on.
つけてね
Follow me.
ついてきて
I followed you.
ついてきた
Do, do, do.
するするする
Can you finish it?
仕上げれる?
this?
これ?
It was sudden.
いきなりだ
Cold
冷め
Ru.
る
cold
冷 め
Ru.
る
amazing.
すごい
Cool down.
冷 める
Does it get cold?
冷める?